<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<data x="20" y="20" width="800" height="450">
	<component type="LineComponent" space="0">
		<component type="ColumnComponent" space="30">
			<component type="TextComponent" space="7">
				<text x="0" width="750" font="SiemensSans" size="28" letterSpacing="0" thickness="-25" sharpness="-25" lineSpacing="0" align="left" color="0xFFFFFF"><![CDATA[Disclaimer]]></text>
			</component>
			<component type="ScrollPanelComponent" space="0" width="760" height="350" x="0" y="0">
				<component type="TextComponent" space="0">
					<text x="0" width="750" font="SiemensSans" size="13" letterSpacing="0" thickness="-25" sharpness="-25" lineSpacing="4" align="left" color="0xFFFFFF"><![CDATA[The documents provided on this website contains forward-looking statements and information – that is, statements related to future, not past, events. These statements may be identified by words such as “expects,” “looks forward to,” “anticipates,” “intends,” “plans,” “believes,” “seeks,” “estimates,” “will,” “project” or words of similar meaning. Such statements are based on the current expectations and certain assumptions of Siemens’ management, and are, therefore, subject to certain risks and uncertainties. A variety of factors, many of which are beyond Siemens’ control, affect Siemens’ operations, performance, business strategy and results and could cause the actual results, performance or achievements of Siemens to be materially different from any future results, performance or achievements that may be expressed or implied by such forward-looking statements. For Siemens, particular uncertainties arise, among others, from: changes in general economic and business conditions (including margin developments in major business areas and recessionary trends); the possibility that customers may delay the conversion of booked orders into revenue or that prices will decline as a result of continued adverse market conditions to a greater extent than currently anticipated by Siemens’ management; developments in the financial markets, including fluctuations in interest and exchange rates, commodity and equity prices, debt prices (credit spreads) and financial assets generally; continued volatility and a further deterioration of the capital markets; a worsening in the conditions of the credit business and, in particular, additional uncertainties arising out of the subprime, financial market and liquidity crises; future financial performance of major industries that Siemens serves, including, without limitation, the Sectors Industry, Energy and Healthcare; the challenges of integrating major acquisitions and implementing joint ventures and other significant portfolio measures; the introduction of competing products or technologies by other companies; a lack of acceptance of new products or services by customers targeted by Siemens; changes in business strategy; the outcome of pending investigations and legal proceedings, including corruption investigations to which Siemens is currently subject and actions resulting from the findings of these investigations; the potential impact of such investigations and proceedings on Siemens’ ongoing business including its relationships with governments and other customers; the potential impact of such matters on Siemens’ financial statements; as well as various other factors. More detailed information about certain of the risk factors affecting Siemens is contained throughout this report and in Siemens’ other filings with the SEC, which are available on the Siemens website, www.siemens.com, and on the SEC’s website, www.sec.gov. Should one or more of these risks or uncertainties materialize, or should underlying assumptions prove incorrect, actual results may vary materially from those described in the relevant forward-looking statement as expected, anticipated, intended, planned, believed, sought, estimated or projected. Siemens does not intend or assume any obligation to update or revise these forward-looking statements in light of developments which differ from those anticipated.<br>New orders; adjusted or organic growth rates of revenue and new orders; the book-to-bill ratio; return on equity, or ROE; return on capital employed, or ROCE; free cash flow; cash conversion rate, or CCR; EBITDA (adjusted); EBIT (adjusted); net debt and adjusted industrial net debt are or may be non-GAAP financial measures. These supplemental financial measures should not be viewed in isolation as alternatives to measures of  Siemens’ financial condition, results of operations or cash flows as presented in accordance with IFRS in its Consolidated Financial Statements. A definition of these supplemental financial measures, a reconciliation to the most directly comparable IFRS financial measures and information regarding the usefulness and limitations of these supplemental financial measures can be found on Siemens’ Investor Relations website at www.siemens.com/nonGAAP.]]></text>
				</component>
			</component>
		</component>
	</component>
</data>